Guide to the Peter Reddaway Samizdat collection, 1950-2010 GRC0002
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Mainstream, Circa 1960s to 1990s; Series 4
  - Individual, Series 4 Subseries 4
    - Shcharansky [Anatoly], 1977 December 22-1997 January 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Shcharansky [Anatoly], 1977 March 15-1986 May 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - [Shchinkova, Tat'iana], 1980 January 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - [Shelkov, Vladimir], 1977 February 23-1980 January 31; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - [Shepelev, Georgii], 1980 November 5-1981 March 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - [Shevchenko, Arkadii], 1979 August 29-1986 March 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - [Shevchuk, Anna], 1981; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - [Shibaev, Sergei], 1977 October 24-1979 July 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - [Shifrin, Avraam], 1976 February 21-1988 July 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Yu[rii] Shikhanovich, 1972 September 29-1985 February 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - [Shilkov, Andrei], 1985 December 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - [Shimanov, Gennadii], 1975 May 29-1976 July 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - [Shinkova, Tat'iana], 1980 January 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - [Shishkin, Anatolii], 1982; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - [Shkarubo, Andrei], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - [Shkolnik, Isaak], 1973 July 3-1973 July 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - [Shostakovich, Maksim], 1981 December 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - [Shovkov, Ivan], 1977; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - [Shpiller, Vsevolod}, 1974 February 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Shragin [Boris], 1972-1974 May 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - [Shramko, Svetlana], 1974 September 30-1975 April 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - [Shreider, Iulii], 1990 January 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - [Shtein, Lubov], 1989 November 14-1989 November 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - [Shtel'makha, Aleksandr], 1968 November 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - [Shubin, Evgenii], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - [Shubin, Evgeny], 1990 November 16-1995 December 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - [Shukevich, Iurii], 1980 February 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - [Shukhevich-Berezynskii, Yuri], 1967 July 28; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - [Shul'gin, Vasilii], 1978 January; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - [Shul'ts, Fedor], 1957 May 8-1965 February 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - [Shumuk, Danilo], 1973 December 4-1978 October 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - [Shutkin, A.F.], 1979 September 28-1980 January 26; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - [Shutov, Iurii], 1990 August 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - [Shutova, Anna Galina], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - [Shvachka, Andrei], 1985 February 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - [Shvahchko, Andrei], 1985 August 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - [Shvartskopf, Vasilii], 1982 March 26; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - [Sichko, Petr], 1979 July 10-1982 July 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - [Sichko, Vasilii], 1978 April-1982 January 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - [Sichko, Vladimir], 1980 November-1981 January 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - [Sidenko, Fyodor], 1974 November 19-1983 February 28; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - [Sidorchuk, Dmitrii], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - [Sil'nitskii, Aleksandr], 1975 August-1975 December 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - [Simchich, Miroslav], 1976-1981 July 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - [Simonishvili, Abesalom], 1980 October 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - [Simun, Vadim], 1979 September 4-1980 August 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - [Simutis, Liudvekas], 1970 July 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - [Siniavin, I.], 1978 August; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - [Siniavskii, Andrei], 1973 November 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - [Sinilnikov, D.L.], 1977 March 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - [Sirotenko, Elena], 1981 February 19-1981 May 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - [Sitnik, Lidiia], 1976 January 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - [Skobov, Aleksandr], 1978 November 15-1984; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - [Skochok, Pavlo], 1987 June 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - [Skubko, Iurii], 1988 June 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - [Skudra, Jan], 1982 January-1983 March 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - [Skulme, Jurgis], 1977 September 30-1978 January 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - [Skuodis, Vytautas], 1980 January 14-1984 August 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - [Skvirskaia, Nelli], 1981 May 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - [Skvirskii, Vladimir], 1978 October 13-1985 October 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - [Sladkevicius, Vincentas], 2000 June 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - [Slepak, Vladimir], 1978 June 6-1982 October 26; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - [Slinin, Aleksandr], 1975 July; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - [Slobodian, M.K.], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - [Slobodskii, Naum], 1985 May 4-1989 March 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - [Smirnov, Aleksei], 1982 September 13-1983 May 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - [Smirnov, Valentin], 1980 July; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 44)
    - [Smirnova, Victoria], 1970 June 2-1972 February 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - [Snegirev, Gelli], 1977 February 28-1979 January; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 46)
    - [Soboleva-Bode, E.], 1981 March 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 47)
    - [Soifer, Valerii], 1982 October 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 48)
    - [Sokirko, Viktor], 1975 May 22-1979 November 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 49)
    - [Sokolov, Andrei], 1975 May 1-1976 December 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - [Sokolov, Valentin], 1981 October 29-1984 November 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - [Sokolov, Viktor], 1975 November 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - [Sokolov, Vladimir], 1973 December 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - [Sokolova, Sof'ia], 1981 February 26; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - [Sokov, Leonid], 1979 June 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - [Soldatov, Sergei], 1975 April-1981 December 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - [Solovev, Oleg], 1982 February; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Solzhenitsyn [Alexander] [1/6], 1968 February 11-1985 February 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Solzhenitsyn [Alexander] [2/6], 1957 February 6-1971 August 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Solzhenitsyn [Alexander] [3/6], 1968 December 12-1973 March 31; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Solzhenitsyn [Alexander] [4/6], 1973 May 21-1976 March 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Solzhenitsyn [Alexander] [5/6], 1972-1980 May; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Solzhenitsyn [Alexander] [6/6], 1969 April 6-2001 June 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - [Soroka, Stepan], 1975 June 3-1975 July 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - [Sorokin, Nikolai], 1979 December-1982 November 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - [Sorokina, Seitkhan], 1978 December 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - [Sosnovskii, Vasilii], 1980 February 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - [Spassky, Boris], 1977 January 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - [Spinenko, Vasilii], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - [Stakenas, Vaclovas], 1985 November 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - [Stankevich, Arsenii], 1983 January 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - [Starchik, Petr], 1973 February-1982 June; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - [Starikov, Dmitrii], 1987 June 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - [Starosel'skii, Vladimir], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - [Starovoitova, Galina], 1988 March 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - [Stashenko, Gregory], 1986 September 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - [Stasiv, Vasyl], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - [Statkiavichius, Al'girdas], 1980 February 8-1988 May 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - [Stepanchuk, Arkhady], 1980 November 4-1980 November 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - [Stepanov, Anatolii], 1981 January; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - [Stepanov, E.F.], 1986 July 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - [Stepanov, Ivan], 1969 December 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - [Stern, Michail], 1974 December 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - [Stolar, Abe], 1985 April 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - [Strelianyi, Anatolii], 1987 May 15-1989 March 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - [Strel'stov, Vasilii], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - [Stril'tsiv, Vasilii], 1979 November 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - [Stroeva, Elena], 1976 February 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - [Strokatova, Nina], 1973 May 17-1976 October 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - [Stus, Vasil'], 1975 June-1987 February 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - [Suchkov, Fedot], 1979 November-1980 December 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - [Sulakvelidze, Merad], 1988 August 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - [Sulimov, Valerii], 1980 August 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Superfin [Garik], 1973 August 14-1982 November 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - [Suprunyuk, G.], 1972 March 15-1973 June 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - [Suslenskii, Iakov], 1970-1976 November 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - [Suslina, Tamara], 1988 May 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - [Svarinskas, Fr. Alfonsas], 1983 January 27-1983 May 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - [Sverskii, Gregorii], 1972 March 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - [Sverstiuk, Evgenii], 1977 May 8- 1978 December 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - [Svetlichnaia, Nadia], 1976 September 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - [Svetlichnii, I.A.], 1977 August 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - [Svetov, Feliks], 1982 August 8-1985 September 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - [Sviklas, Antanas-Remigiius], 1984 January 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - [Svitlichnii, Ivan], 1973-1978; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 42)
    - [Sysoev, Viacheslav], 1980-1984 May 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 43)
    - [Sytin], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 44)
    - [Sytinskii, Vladimir], 1985 February; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 45)
    - [Talalai, Mikhail], 1988 May 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 46)
    - [Tamkevicius, Fr. Sisitas], 1983 December 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 47)
    - [Tarasov, Adrian], 1973 November; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 48)
    - [Tarasova, Raisa], 1990 February 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 49)
    - [Tarkovskii, Andrei], 1984 July 11-1984 December 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 50)
    - [Tatos, Artin], 1977 June 1-1977 July 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 51)
    - [Telegin, Semen], 1972 September 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 52)
    - [Telesin, Iulilus], 1970 February 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 53)
    - [Telessin, Ziame], 1971 August 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 51, Folder 54)
    - Temkin [Alexander], 1972 October 25-1976 September 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - [Temkin, Marina], 1979 September 21-1979 Septmber 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - [Tendriakov, Vladimir], 1984 August 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - [Terelia, Iosif], 1977 March 23-1986 July 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - [Terliatskas, Antanas], 1975 November 23-1983; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - [Ternovskii, Evgenii], 1974; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - [Ternovskii, Leonard], 1971 September 21-1982 January 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - [Tesker, Zakhar], 1977 September 30-1977 December 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - [Tesmenitskii, Leonid], 1981 August 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - [Tetenov, Nikolai], 1971 October 9-1978 January 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - [Tikhii, Oleksii], 1976 August 18-1984 June 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - [Timofeev, Lev], 1985 March 29-1988 January 28; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - [Timokhin, Sergei], 1983 October 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - [Timoshenko, Mikhail], 1986 June 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - [Tishchenko, I.P.], 1987 February 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - [Titov, Vladimir], 1981 February 3-1984 September 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - [Titov, Vladimir], 1985 March 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - [Tiurichev, Valerii], 1981 August 11-1986 October 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - [Tokaiuk, Grigorii], 1978 February 2-1979 August 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - [Tolmachev, Nikolai], 1979 September; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - [Tomachinskii, Viktor], 1978 November-1982 March 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - [Tretiakova, Tamara], 1985 April 10-1985 April 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - [Trifonov, Iurii], 1977 December 7-1981 April 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - [Troianskii, Sergei], 1981 June 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - [Trusovaia, Tat'iana], 1981 September 8-1984 May; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - [Tsapenko, P.], 1978 November 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - [Tsapurin, Igor'], 1981 November 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - [Tsarukian, Garnik], 1984 March 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - [Tsirkunenko, N.B.], 1984 October 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - [Tsirlin, Aleksandr], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - [Tsitlenok, Boris], 1977 December 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - [Tsivileva, Avgusta], 1982 February 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - [Tsivin, Mikhail], 1982 March 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - Tsukerman [Boris], 1968 December 5-1972 May 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 34)
    - [Tsukerman, Vladimir], 1981; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - [Tsurkov, Arkadii], 1979 April 19-1987 November; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - [Tsurkova, Irina], 1979 September 28-1983 March 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - [Tsyrikov, Vladimir], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Tumerman [Alexei], 1972 May 22-1973 May 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - [Turchenko, Iurii], 1980 February 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - V[alentin] Turchin, 1968 June 28-1977 October; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - [Tvadadze, O.V.], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - [Tvardovskii, Aleksandr], 1968 October-1975 June 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - [Tverdokhlebov, Andrei], 1969-1976 September 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - [Tymanova, Lina], 1981 September 6-1985 April 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - [Tymchuk, Leonid], 1968 January 15-1968 October 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - [Tyryshkin, V.S.], 1990 March 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - [Tyurichev, Valery], 1983 March 18-1986 May 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - [Ubozhko, Dr.], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - [Udam, Erik], 1976 May 26-1977 June; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - [Udodov, Aleksandr], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - [Ukhtomskaia, Galina], 1980 December 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - [Ulanovskii, Lev], 1977 July 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - [Umanskii, Boris], 1963 May 26-1963 July 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - [Unksov, Kari], 1981 January 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - [Urin, Viktor], 1976 June 9-1976 June 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - US Army Institute for Avanced Russian and East European Studies - Student Research Report, 1973 October; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - [Ushakov, Aleksandr], 1986 July 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - [Ushakov, German], 1976 July 28-1977 February 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - [Usoeva, Nadezhda], 1980 December; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - [Utemov, Mikhail], 1981 December 16-1982 February 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - [Vagin, Evgenii], 1976 August 13-1977 April 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - [Vagner, Viktor], 1987 January 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - [Valendo, Lidiia], 1978 November 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - [Valitova, Irina], 1977 March 16-1982 January 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - [Val'lman, Iokhannes], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - [Valov, Iurii], 1979 April; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - [Van' Si Pin], 1980 July 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - [Van Voren, [Robert]], 1988 April 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - [Vardomtsev, Viktor], 1980 October-1981 March; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - [Varlygina, V.A.], 1988 April 26; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - [Vartanov, Iliia], 1988 December; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - [Varvak, Liliana], 1980 May 18-1981 January 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - [Vashchenko, Lida], 1982 February 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - [Vasil'ev, Viktor], 1977 May 6-1977 December 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - [Vasilik, Vladimir], 1978-1979; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - [Vasil'surskii, Episkop Varnav], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - [Vavilov, Nikolai], 1978 December 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - [Velikanov, Viacheslav], 1976 January 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - [Velikanova, Tatiana], 1975 December 26-2002 October 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - [Velikoredchanin, Stanislav], 1990 December 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - [Venclova, Tomas], 1976 February 6-1976 April 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - [Vereshagina, A.N.], 1984 January 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - [Verkholiak, Dmitro], 1976 June; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - [Verkholian, D.N.], 1978 October 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - [Verkhovskii, Anatolii], 1987 August; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - [Verner, Peter], 1978 April 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - [Vernik, Ivan], 1977 April 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - [Vilenskaia, Larisa], 1977 November 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - [Vins, Georgi], 1979 April 30-1988 November; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - [Vins, Petr], 1977 December 31-1979 April 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - [Vite, Oleg], 1990 January 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - [Vitenas, Pranas], 1986; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - [Vitenko, Aleksandr], 1990 March 26; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - [Vladian, Konstantin], 1977 January 29-1977 April 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - [Vladianu, Knostantin], 1977 January 29-1977 March 28; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - [Vladimov, Georgii], 1969 November 12-1983 May 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - [Vlasenko, Iurii], 1979 March 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - [Vlasov, Anatolii], 1977 October 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - [Voikhanskii, Misha], 1978 May 24-1979 April 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Voinovich [Vladimir], 1973 October 2-1984 February 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - [Volchek, Dmitrii], 1989 January 26; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - [Volik, Ivan], 1975 April 23-1987 May 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - [Vol'khin, Valerii], 1980 October 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - [Volkov, Oleg], 1986 June; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - [Volkov, Yegor], 1983-1985 March; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - [Vol'nii, K], 1971 June 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - [Volokhonskii, Lev], 1979 March 14-1987 October 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - [Voloshanovich, Aleksandr], 1978 November-1979 June 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - Voloshanovich [,Alexander] (1/4], 1978 August 16-1981 June; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Voloshanovich [,Alexander] (2/4], 1977 October 17-1981 December; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Voloshanovich [,Alexander] (3/4], 1978 February 1-1979 February 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Voloshanovich [,Alexander] (4/4], 1979 May 18-1981 April 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - [Voloshchuk, A.A.], 1977 March 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - [Volpin, Aleksandr], 1972 June 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - [Volvovskii, Leonid], 1977 July 20-1985 November 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - [Vorona, Aleksandr], 1979 May 6-1984 December 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 40)
    - [Voronina, Lidia], 1975 October 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 41)
    - [Voronov, Aleksandr], 1986 June 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - [Vorozhbit, Evgenii or Mikhail], 1979 February 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - [Voznesenskaia, Iuliia], 1976-1977 April 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - [Voznesenskii, Andrei], 1987 March 18-1988 February 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - [Vudka, Iurii], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Vysotsky [Vladimir], 1970 February 26-1988 January 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - [Wallneberg, Raul], 1978 September 13-1991 September 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - [Weinbaun, Leopold], 1979 August 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 8)